HELLO.
Chandler:
Hey, it's me.
You can't stand
to be in the same room as me
so I thought I'd apologize
over the phone. All...
( rings )
HELLO.
Chandler:
Look, I never should have...
and I'm...
( ringing )
STOP CALLING!
( Chandler as deejay ):
Hey, hey, hey!
This is 92.3 WXRK, K-Rock
calling with our $1,000
daily challenge.
ALL RIGHT.
What is the name
of your roommate
who is very, very sorry
and would do anything...?
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
UGH... TURKEY.
UGH, GIVING THANKS.
UGH!
LOOK, EVERYONE.
IT'S THE SPIRIT
OF THANKSGIVING.
SO, ARE THINGS
WITH YOU AND JOEY ANY BETTER?
THEY COULDN'T BE WORSE.
I SPENT EIGHT HOURS
CALLING HIM LAST NIGHT
TRYING TO GET HIM
TO TALK TO ME.
OH, WOW.
EIGHT HOURS-- SO, YOU
COULD PROBABLY REALLY USE
ONE OF THOSE PLUG-IN
TELEPHONE HEADSETS, HUH?
SHOULD WE ALL EXPECT
CHRISTMAS GIFTS
THAT CAN BE STOLEN
FROM YOUR OFFICE?
YOU SHOULDN'T.
SPEAKING OF CHRISTMAS
SINCE MONICA AND I
ARE STARTING A NEW BUSINESS
AND HAVE, LIKE, NO MONEY
UM, THIS YEAR MAYBE
WE COULD DO SECRET SANTA
AND THEN WE EACH
ONLY BUY ONE GIFT
AND-AND THERE'S
THE ADDED MYSTERY
OF, YOU KNOW,
WHO GETS WHO.
WHO GETS WHOM.
I DON'T KNOW
WHY I DO THAT.
OH, I'M GOING
TO TAKE A NAP.
TURKEY MAKES ME SLEEPY.
WE HAVEN'T
EATEN YET.
I KNOW, BUT ALL THAT WORK
YOU'RE DOING
TO GET IT READY AND I JUST...
HEY, BY ANY CHANCE
DID EITHER OF YOU
PICK RACHEL
FOR YOUR SECRET SANTA?
'CAUSE I WANT
TO TRADE FOR HER.
I PICKED HER.
OOH, THANK GOD, YOU WANT HER.
OOH!
WOW. WHY DO YOU WANT TO GET
RID OF HER SO BADLY?
BECAUSE SHE EXCHANGES
EVERY GIFT SHE EVER GETS.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO GET HER
ANYTHING SHE LIKES.
COME ON, LET'S TRADE!
OH, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I GOT HER THAT BACKPACK,
AND SHE LOVED IT.
I REMEMBER HOW MUCH
SHE WAS CRYING THE DAY
THAT BIG DOG
RAN OFF WITH...
WELL, THERE WAS
NO BIG DOG.
ALL RIGHT, THIS SUCKS
'CAUSE I ALREADY GOT HER
THIS BRIEFCASE, AND I HAD
"R.G." PUT ON IT.
HER INITIALS.
OH.
MAYBE YOU
CAN GIVE IT
TO SOMEBODY ELSE.
OH, LIKE ROSS GELLER.
OH, YOU KNOW
WHAT, THOUGH?
IT'S KIND OF A
GIRLY BRIEFCASE.
WHO CARES?
HE WORKS IN A MUSEUM.
HEY, WHAT TIME IS IT?
THE BIG GAME IS
ABOUT TO START.
ROSS AND JOEY AREN'T HERE.
YOU CAN WATCH THE PARADE
IF YOU WANT.
THANKS.
WHAT IS WRONG
WITH THIS FREEZER?
OW! OW!
GOD, WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, MY GOD,
ICE JUST GOT
IN MY EYE!
PEOPLE ARE TRYING
TO SLEEP IN HERE.
MONICA GOT ICE
IN HER EYE,
AND IT HURTS.
OPEN IT UP.
LET ME SEE.
OH, I CAN'T.
IT REALLY KILLS.
WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
PUT SOME ICE
ON IT.
OOH, IT
LOOKS BAD.
HONEY, MAYBE WE
SHOULD TAKE YOU
TO A DOCTOR.
NO. MY EYE DOCTOR IS RICHARD.
I CAN'T GO TO HIM
WHEN I DON'T HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
HE'S REALLY PICKY
ABOUT HIS PATIENTS.
OKAY, YOU'VE GOT TO GO.
WHAT'S HIS OFFICE NUMBER?
LIKE, I REMEMBER
HIS OFFICE NUMBER.
SPEED DIAL SEVEN.
HI. YEAH, I'M CALLING ON BEHALF
OF MONICA GELLER'S EYE, AND...
IS, UM...
IS RICHARD BURKE IN TODAY?
HE'S OUT OF TOWN, BUT DOES SHE
WANT TO SEE THE ON-CALL DOCTOR?
YES!
YES! SHE'S VERY EXCITED
ABOUT THAT.
THIS IS SO COOL.
TILL MONICA GETS BACK
IT'S, LIKE,
I'M HEAD CHEF
AND I GET TO MAKE
ALL THE DECISIONS.
HEY, HEY,
I THOUGHT
SHE TOLD YOU
TO FOLLOW
THE RECIPE
EXACTLY.
OKAY, GET
OUT OF MY KITCHEN.
ALL RIGHT, I THINK I AM MAKING
SOME PROGRESS WITH JOEY.
WHEN I WENT
INTO THE APARTMENT
HE WENT STRAIGHT
INTO HIS BEDROOM
BUT HE ONLY SLAMMED
THE DOOR ONCE.
WOW.
I MEAN, YEAH, HE GAVE ME
THE FINGER WHILE DOING IT.
ALL RIGHT, I'VE...
I GOT TO CALL MY MOM
AND ASK HER
A LEFT-HANDED COOKING QUESTION.
SO, LISTEN, UH, I PICKED MONICA
FOR SECRET SANTA
BUT I'M ALREADY GETTING HER
SOMETHING FOR HANUKAH.
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU WANT TO SWITCH.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WAS TRYING TO TRADE
FOR, UH... WELL, YOU.
REALLY?
WOW, THAT'S... THAT'S SO NICE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO GET ME?
I DON'T KNOW, R.G.
I THOUGHT SOMETHING GIRLY
FOR YOUR OFFICE.
YEAH.
WELL, MAYBE PHOEBE
WILL SWITCH WITH ME.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO DO THAT.
YOU'LL GET STUCK
WITH RACHEL.
SHE EXCHANGES
EVERY GIFT SHE GETS.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I GOT HER LOTS
OF STUFF SHE
NEVER TOOK BACK.
LIKE?
LIKE THAT GOLD NECKLACE
I GOT HER LAST YEAR.
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
SHE WORE IT?
WELL, SHE WORE IT ALL
CHRISTMAS DAY, AND THEN, UH...
BIG DOG?
HI.
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SENDING BACK THIS STUFF
CHANDLER BOUGHT OUT OF GUILT.
EVERYTHING?
EVEN THE TV?
NO. I'M GOING TO PUT THAT
IN MY ROOM.
LISTEN, JOEY...
I KNOW WHAT
HE DID WAS WRONG
BUT DON'T YOU THINK
YOU COULD AT LEAST
HEAR THE GUY OUT?
BACK WHEN YOU AND RACHEL
WERE TOGETHER
IF CHANDLER HAD KISSED HER
WOULD YOU
HEAR HIM OUT?
GOOD POINT.
SO, UH, HOW LONG ARE YOU
GOING TO PUNISH HIM?
FIVE YEARS.
YOU'VE SENTENCED HIM?
HEY, DON'T DO THE CRIME
IF YOU CAN'T DO THE TIME.
JOEY, THE GUY IS
YOUR BEST FRIEND.
WAS MY BEST FRIEND.
ANYWAY, I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU'RE
PUSHING FOR HIM SO HARD.
WITH HIM OUT OF THE WAY
AS MY BEST FRIEND
THERE'S A SPOT OPEN.
WELL, WHO, ME?
YEAH.
( chuckling )
WOW. I'M HONORED.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'LL DO
AS MY FIRST ACT
AS YOUR BEST FRIEND?
WHAT?
I'M GOING TO GET YOU
TO TALK
TO CHANDLER.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, BUT IF YOU WEREN'T
MY BEST FRIEND...
YEAH...
OH, MY GOD. IS IT
REALLY THAT BAD?
I WALK INTO THE ROOM,
AND HE WON'T EVEN TALK TO ME.
HE'LL JUST MUMBLE
SOMETHING IN ITALIAN...
AND I KNOW HE ONLY
KNOWS THE BAD WORDS.
HEY, GUNTHER,
HAVE YOU, UH...
HAVE YOU SEEN
CHANDLER?
I THOUGHT
YOU WERE CHANDLER.
BUT, UM, ONE OF YOU
IS OVER THERE.
OH.
HEY, JOE.
VA FA A NAPOLI, HUH?!
I'LL BE RIGHT WITH YOU, OKAY?
THANKS FOR COMING IN.
SURE.
OH, MY GOD.
HOW CUTE IS THE
ON-CALL DOCTOR?
OH, SO CUTE
THAT I'M THINKING
ABOUT JAMMING THIS PEN
IN MY EYE.
( intercom buzzes )
DR. BURKE WILL SEE YOU NOW.
OH, NO, NOT DR. BURKE.
DR. BURKE'S
OUT OF TOWN.
THE ON-CALL DOCTOR
WILL SEE ME NOW.
DR. RICHARD BURKE
IS OUT OF TOWN.
DR. TIMOTHY BURKE, HIS SON,
WILL SEE YOU NOW.
READY?
HEY, I'M SORRY.
THAT...
WHERE YOU GOING?
MY FOLKS'.
OH. UH... WHEN YOU,
WHEN YOU COMING BACK?
I DON'T KNOW.
I MIGHT STAY THERE
FOR A FEW DAYS
WHILE I LOOK
FOR AN APARTMENT.
WHAT?
AT FIRST I THOUGHT
WE COULD TALK ABOUT THIS
YOU KNOW, WORK IT OUT
BUT SEEING YOU TWO
TOGETHER AND ALL...
HEY, LOOK,
WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO SAY?
DO YOU WANT ME
TO SAY I'LL
STOP SEEING HER?
IT'S NOT ABOUT HER, OKAY?
BUT SEEING YOU TWO TOGETHER
JUST REMINDS ME OF WHAT YOU DID
AND I DON'T WANT TO LIVE
WITH SOMEONE WHO DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT IT IS TO BE A FRIEND,
SO I'LL SEE YOU.
LOOK, I KNOW WHAT IT IS
TO BE A FRIEND.
I JUST... I SCREWED UP.
YEAH, YOU DID...
AND THAT'S WHY
I'M LEAVING.
( quacking )
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
IF YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO STAY FOR ME
THEN AT LEAST
STAY FOR THEM.
OKAY, THEY HAVE HAD
A VERY DIFFICULT YEAR
WHAT WITH THE ROBBERY AND ALL.
WHEN THAT GUY
WAS ROBBING US
AND I WAS LOCKED IN
THE ENTERTAINMENT UNIT
FOR SIX HOURS,
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT I WAS DOING IN
THERE ALL THAT TIME?
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
HOW I LET YOU DOWN.
WOW.
YEAH, BUT IF
I'D KNOWN
WHAT KIND OF FRIEND
YOU WOULD TURN OUT TO BE
I WOULDN'T HAVE WORRIED
SO MUCH ABOUT IT.
SEE YOU AROUND.
JUST WAIT
ONE SECOND NOW.
THERE HAS TO BE SOMETHING
THAT I CAN DO, SOMETHING.
IF WE STILL HAD
THAT ENTERTAINMENT UNIT
I WOULD GET IN THERE
FOR SIX HOURS AND THINK
ABOUT HOW I LET YOU DOWN.
WHAT?
WE GOT A BOX.
I REMEMBER
THE LAST TIME I SAW YOU.
IT WAS THE MORNING
I LEFT FOR COLLEGE
AND YOU WERE JUST STANDING
OUTSIDE THE DAIRY QUEEN.
I WAS JUST PROBABLY
WAITING FOR IT TO OPEN.
GOT TO TELL YOU,
YOU LOOK GREAT NOW.
YOU LOOK GREAT, TOO.
YOU'RE AN EXCELLENT PATIENT.
SO HOW DOES IT LOOK?
YOU'VE GOT A LITTLE SCRATCH
ON YOUR CORNEA.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO WEAR A PATCH.
LIKE A PIRATE?
IF THAT HELPS YOU.
OOH.
( clears throat )
SO HOW LONG YOU BEEN WORKING
WITH YOUR DAD?
COME ON. ONE OF US
HAD TO MENTION HIM.
I MOVED BACK HERE
A COUPLE MONTHS AGO.
BIG FAMILY
DINNER TONIGHT?
UH, HERE.
OH, NO WAY.
I WAS GOING TO
HAVE THANKSGIVING
AT MY GIRLFRIEND'S...
OH.
BUT WE BROKE UP.
OH?
SHE-SHE WASN'T READY
FOR A SERIOUS COMMITMENT.
OH...
( gruffly ):
SO YOU MADE HER
WALK THE PLANK, AYE, MATEY?
YOU'RE NOT WEARING
THE PATCH YET.
I KNOW.
HE'S COMING HERE
FOR THANKSGIVING?
I KNOW. IT'S SICK.
WHY'S IT SICK?
BECAUSE IT'S RICHARD'S SON.
IT'S LIKE INVITING
A GREEK TRAGEDY OVER FOR DINNER.
I MEAN, COME
ON, PHOEBE.
YOU UNDERSTAND,
DON'T YOU?
YEAH, I COULD SEE
WHERE I'D BE
YOUR BEST SHOT, BUT NO.
NO, I'M SORRY, HONEY.
I THINK IT'S TWISTED.
WHAT'S TWISTED?
ME GOING OUT
WITH RICHARD'S SON.
EWW!
EWW, EWW, EWW!
Chandler:
SOUNDS LIKE
A REALLY BAD
IDEA TO ME.
IS HE OKAY
IN THERE?
( firmly ):
HE'S FINE.
HEY, YOU KNOW, MON
IF THINGS WORK OUT
BETWEEN YOU AND RICHARD'S SON
YOU'D BE ABLE TO TELL YOUR KIDS
THAT YOU SLEPT
WITH THEIR GRANDFATHER.
FINE. JUDGE ALL YOU WANT TO
BUT MARRIED A LESBIAN
LEFT A MAN
AT THE ALTAR
FELL IN LOVE WITH
A GAY ICE DANCER
THREW A GIRL'S WOODEN LEG
IN THE FIRE
LIVE IN A BOX!
SO, NOW, WHAT EXACTLY
IS THE POINT OF THE BOX?
CHANDLER?
THE MEANING OF THE BOX
IS THREEFOLD.
ONE:
IT GIVES ME THE TIME
TO THINK ABOUT WHAT I DID.
TWO:
IT PROVES
HOW MUCH I CARE
ABOUT MY FRIENDSHIP
WITH JOEY.
AND THREE:
IT HURTS.
OH, HEY.
HEY, UH, DO YOU REMEMBER
THAT NECKLACE
I GAVE YOU LAST YEAR?
CAN I SEE IT?
WHY?
I WANT TO CHECK SOMETHING.
OKAY.
NOW WE'LL SEE.
AIR HOLE! AIR HOLE!
SORRY.
HERE IT IS. I LOVE IT.
I WEAR IT
ALL THE TIME.
THE NECKLACE
I GOT YOU WAS GOLD.
THIS IS SILVER.
HUH.
WELL, MAYBE IT, UH...
IT CHANGED.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU ACTUALLY EXCHANGED IT.
ISN'T IT BETTER
THAT I EXCHANGE IT
FOR SOMETHING
THAT I ENJOY
AND CAN GET A LOT
OF USE OUT OF?
WHAT DID YOU GET?
CREDIT.
( knock at door )
I'LL GET IT. I'LL GET IT.
HI, TIM.
HI.
HI. THANK YOU.
MEET MY FRIENDS.
THIS IS, UH, PHOEBE.
HI. NICE TO MEET YOU.
AND JOEY.
HEY.
MY BROTHER, ROSS.
AND RACHEL.
( Chandler clears throat )
THAT'S CHANDLER.
HOW DO YOU DO?
WHAT'S...?
WELL, HE'S, UM...
HE'S DOING SOME THINKING.
Commentator:
McCallister tries...
YEAH!
YES!
Chandler:
WHAT HAPPENED? WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU KISSED
MY GIRLFRIEND.
OOH, I LIKE
THOSE SUNGLASSES.
"LIKE THEM" LIKE THEM
OR "I'D LIKE TO GET STORE CREDIT
FOR THAT AMOUNT"
LIKE THEM?
VA FA A NAPOLI.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY;
THIS TURKEY IS READY.
WHERE CAN I WASH UP?
HERE. LET ME SHOW YOU.
OKAY, THE TOWELS ARE HANGING
NEXT TO THE SINK
AND YOU CAN USE
THE FANCY SOAP.
THANK YOU.
"FANCY SOAP"?
I THOUGHT WE WERE
SAVING THAT FOR THE POPE.
SEE? HE'S NICE, RIGHT?
BUT DO YOU REALLY WANT
TO BE IN A RELATIONSHIP
WHERE YOU CAN USE THE PHRASE
"THAT'S NOT HOW YOUR DAD
USED TO DO IT"?
WOW. EVERYTHING
LOOKS GREAT.
WHERE SHOULD I SIT?
SAVED YOU A SEAT.
SICK, SICK, SICK,
SICK, SICK.
( knock at door )
OH, I'LL GET IT.
Chandler:
GOTCHA!
( laughing )
THAT DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE THINKING TO ME.
SORRY.
I DON'T THINK YOU
SHOULD BE TALKING AT ALL.
I THINK YOU GOT
TOO MUCH THINKING TO DO
TO BE TALKING
AND MAKING JOKES.
OKAY, OKAY. YOU GOT IT.
ROSS, COULD YOU
PASS ME THE YAMS?
OH, AND JOEY'S GOT
THE MASHED POTATOES
IF YOU WANT TO EXCHANGE THEM.
WILL YOU STOP?
WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH YOU?
( fake laugh ):
OH, WE'VE GOT COMPANY.
THERE'S NOTHING
THE MATTER WITH ME.
SEE, I'M NOT COMPLETELY DEVOID
OF SENTIMENT.
SEE, I HAVE FEELINGS.
OKAY, FINE.
YOU CAN'T TELL, BUT I'M TRYING
TO BREAK THE TENSION
BY MOONING YOU GUYS.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
IF THIS IS JUST A BIG JOKE
TO YOU, THEN FORGET ABOUT IT.
ALL RIGHT,
THIS MEANS SOMETHING TO ME.
IF IT DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING
TO YOU
THEN YOU SHOULD GET
OUT OF THERE.
OTHERWISE, YOU'RE JUST
AN IDIOT IN A BOX.
YOU'RE RIGHT,
AND I'M SORRY.
THIS MEANS
A LOT TO ME.
I WANT YOU TO BE
MY FRIEND AGAIN.
I SWEAR I WON'T
SAY ANOTHER
WORD TONIGHT.
SO YOU'RE GOING TO START
TAKING THIS THING SERIOUSLY?
ABSOLUTELY.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE
ANOTHER WORD TO ME.
ARE YOU GOING
TO TAKE THIS SERIOUSLY?
OKAY.
DON'T SAY
THAT I HAVE NO SENTIMENT.
THIS IS A MOVIE STUB
FROM OUR FIRST DATE.
THIS IS AN EGGSHELL
FROM THE FIRST TIME YOU
MADE ME BREAKFAST IN BED.
THIS IS FROM THE MUSEUM
THE FIRST TIME...
WE WERE TOGETHER.
OKAY, MAYBE
I EXCHANGE
GIFTS SOMETIMES
BUT I KEEP THE
THINGS THAT MATTER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I'M SORRY.
THOUGH...
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO TAKE THESE.
IT'S, LIKE,
A MILLION YEARS OLD.
WE... WE ACTUALLY...
WE HAVE PEOPLE
LOOKING FOR THAT.
OH, THIS ALWAYS HAPPENS.
HERE. LET ME, UM...
THANK YOU.
YOU HAVE VERY BEAUTIFUL...
EYE.
YOU KNOW, MY FRIENDS
ALL THINK THIS IS WEIRD.
I THOUGHT IT WAS
GOING TO BE WEIRD.
I ALMOST CALLED TO CANCEL,
BUT IT REALLY ISN'T.
I KNOW. IT'S LIKE
YOU AND YOUR DAD--
THAT'S A TOTALLY
SEPARATE THING.
OH, I TOTALLY AGREE.
WE'RE JUST TWO PEOPLE
WHO FIND EACH OTHER...
VERY ATTRACTIVE.
RIGHT?
WHAT?
NOTHING. NOTHING.
NO. NO, REALLY--
WAS THAT NOT OKAY?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
THAT WAS GOOD.
THAT WAS, UH...
THAT WAS A GOOD KISS.
MY GOD. IT DIDN'T
REMIND YOU OF MY...?
OH, DON'T SAY IT!
NO, BUT IT DID,
DIDN'T IT?
YES!
OH, MAN!
( groaning )
I KNOW!
( both shudder loudly )
Commentator:
...that's 18 yards.
Is he having quite a day.
( loud shudder )
( knock at door )
I GOT IT.
OH.
HEY.
LISTEN. I WANT YOU TO KNOW
HOW SORRY I AM...
THAT'S OKAY.
CHANDLER'S THE ONE
I'M MAD AT, SO...
WELL, I'M STILL SORRY.
IS HE HERE?
IN THE BOX.
HI.
CHANDLER?
OH, HE CAN'T TALK
RIGHT NOW.
WHY NOT?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HE'S TRYING
TO SHOW JOEY
HOW MUCH
HE MEANS TO HIM.
BY BEING IN A BOX.
JOEY HAD REASONS.
THEY WERE THREEFOLD.
OH. WELL, UH...
YOU NOT BEING
ABLE TO TALK
MIGHT ACTUALLY
MAKE THIS EASIER.
LISTEN, UM...
LISTEN.
I DON'T WANT TO BE SOMEONE
WHO COMES
BETWEEN TWO BEST FRIENDS.
I JUST... I CAN'T STAND SEEING
WHAT THIS IS DOING TO YOU GUYS
AND I DON'T WANT TO BE
THE CAUSE OF THAT.
SO... I DON'T THINK
WE CAN SEE EACH OTHER ANYMORE.
I'M GOING TO GO
TO MY MOM'S
IN CHICAGO.
I'M GOING TO STAY THERE
FOR A WHILE.
I THINK THIS COULD HAVE BEEN
SOMETHING REALLY AMAZING.
( laughs softly )
BUT, YOU KNOW,
THIS IS PROBABLY FOR THE BEST.
YOU KNOW?
I'M GOING TO MISS YOU.
GOOD-BYE, CHANDLER.
( door closes )
( moaning ):
OPEN THE BOX!
Rachel:
WHAT?
HE CAN STILL CATCH HER!
HEY, COME ON.
GET OUT OF THERE!
SO...?
YEAH, WE'RE GOING
TO BE FINE. GET OUT.
YEAH?
YEAH. YOU DID SOME
REAL GOOD THINKING IN THERE.
I MEAN, THIS IS...
( mumbles )
NOW, GO 'CAUSE YOU
CAN STILL CATCH HER
AND MERRY CHRISTMAS
FROM YOUR SECRET SANTA!
ALL RIGHT, WHO GOT CHANDLER,
'CAUSE I NEED TO TRADE.
OH, HE SEES HER.
OH, HE'S CATCHING
UP TO HER.
OH, SHE SEES HIM.
OH, THEY'RE HUGGING.
OHH.
HE'S TAKING
HER PURSE.
UH, THAT'S
NOT THEM.
I'M GOING TO GO
CALL THE POLICE.
OH, THERE THEY ARE!
WHERE? OH...
( all sighing )
ALL RIGHT,
GET A ROOM.